romancecompass.com 2016-01-29

# Privacy Policy

Sono RC LP is a registered company(referred to in this Privacy Policy as "we" and "our" and "us"), whose dating services are provided on a domain [www.romancecompass.com](http://www.romancecompass.com/)

This Privacy Policy must be read together with our Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to, as it sets out how we process data collected from you or which you provide to us in relation to the Sono RC LP Company dating services ("Dating Services").

BY REGISTERING AND BECOMING A MEMBER SUBSCRIBING TO OUR DATING SITE SERVICES, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION, RETENTION, DISTRIBUTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BY US IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS.

  **Statement**

For the general use of our Dating Site we do not store or capture any personal data, other than to log your IP address, session details, the number of pages you view, type of browser you use and your general internet use which we store in a cookie file so we can continue to develop and improve the Dating Services we provide to you.

Where you give us any information or personal data for the Dating Site through membership registration or instruct us in any other way, you are granting us permission to store and process the information you give us for the purpose of providing you with our Dating Services and/or similar services provided by third parties carefully selected by us.

  **Information we may collect from you**

We may collect and process personal data about you to include information you provide us by filling in forms, over the telephone, when you register with our Dating Site or from similar services of third parties connected with us, email us, use our Dating Site when participating in promotions, entering competitions or in any other manner by which you provide your personal details to us.

**IP addresses and cookies**

We may collect information about your computer, to include your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration which is statistical information but we do not collect your personal details. For the same reason we may obtain information about your general internet use on a cookie file which is software stored on the hard drive of your computer and recalls details of how your computer operates. Cookies help us improve our Dating Services to you and help us deliver a more personalised service to you since cookies enable us to estimate our audience size, track your usage pattern, store information about your preferences and allows us to customise our Dating Site to your individual interests and to also recognise you when you return to our Dating Site.

You may refuse cookies by changing the settings on your computer browser. For precise instructions appropriate to your web browser select "help" from your menu bar and search for cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If however you do not accept cookies you may not be able to access some features on our Dating Site such as the delivery of dating advertisements, pop-ups and sub-sites, as well as the transactional elements of the Dating Services we provide. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

**Sensitive Information Handling**

We use HTTPS/SSL encryption is to ensure customers' sensitive data is protected.  
Credit card details submitted by customers are handled securely to ensure confidentiality.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be revised or updated by us from time to time please read these terms on our Dating Site frequently to keep yourself up-to-date with any changes we make.

  **Use of your personal information**

Your personal information, including contact information such as postal and email addresses and telephone numbers, may be used by us for any of our internal purposes, including for instance administration, site updates or upgrades, editorial purposes, promotions, marketing of goods and services, statistical analysis and market research or for evaluating the use made of our websites

**Disclosure of personal information to third parties**

Your personal information will be disclosed only where we are obliged or permitted to do so by law, or in any circumstances described in our Terms & Conditions. We may disclose non-personally identifiable data to commercial advertisers on our websites or any other of our commercial clients to help them understand and meet potential customer preferences and needs

**Retention of personal information**

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data on our Dating Site, we cannot guarantee security of your data transmitted over the internet. You transfer your data at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential and we ask you not to share your password with anyone. We will act as quickly as possible to resolve any security breach of which we become aware. We will keep your personal information for as long as is necessary to provide you with our Dating Services. You may ask us to remove your details and cancel your membership to our Dating Site at any time (subject to any cancellation fees which apply), but we may need to keep your details for a minimum of 12 months or such other period as is reasonably required by law. You are entitled to request personal data that we hold about you for a small charge. You can insist that we correct any information we hold about you.

  **Third party policies**

Third parties and websites linked to our site may collect or use information about you. We are not liable for the information practices of unconnected companies or other persons except as may be required by law

If you need to contact us for any reason, please do so at the following address:

**Sono RC LP**

**16/5 West Pilton Rise,  **

**Edinburgh,  **

**EH4 4UQ,  **

**United Kingdom**
